I eat ice cream every single night while
maintaining a caloric deficit. Here's
how I do it. I use the Ninja Creamy
Swirl to recreate my favorite ice cream
flavors in a much healthier way. Here
are five of the flavors I made this
week. In honor of St. Patrick's Day, I
recreated McDonald's Shamrock Shake. I
followed that up by using the best
Pop-Tart flavor, brown sugar cinnamon,
to create this flavor, which was a
cinnamon base with a brown sugar
pop-tart mixed in. Then I did a Nutella
flavor, basically just a chocolate
hazelnut base. and it was just so rich
and creamy and decadent. This one was
phenomenal. Then I had to hop on the
strawberry matcha trend. So this was a
strawberry protein ice cream base with a
white chocolate matcha hard shell. You
can just crack it into little pieces,
break it up. It's so so good. And then I
ended off the week with a Oreo Shamrock
McFlurry. Another McDonald's recreation
and one of my favorite recipes of all